A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, Projects (Grants), RG 3, Subgroup 1 and Subgroup 2 FA005
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Projects (Grants), 1947-1996; 3; 750 Cubic Feet
  - Projects (Grants), 1947-1989; 1
    - Big Sisters, Inc., 1961-1965 (Box 153, Folder 1020)
    - Big Sisters, Inc., 1966-1969 (Box 153, Folder 1021)
    - Big Sisters, Inc., 1970-1975 (Box 153, Folder 1022)
    - Big Sisters, Inc., 1977-1979 (Box 153, Folder 1023)
    - Big Sisters, Inc., Tax Information, 1970-1973 (Box 153, Folder 1024)
    - Bio-Energy Council, 1978-June 1982 (Box 153, Folder 1025)
    - Bio-Energy Council, 1982 July-December (Box 154, Folder 1025A)
    - Blind Service Agency of Westchester, 1960-1962 (Box 154, Folder 1026)
    - Bloomingdale House of Music, 1970-1976 (Box 154, Folder 1027)
    - Bloomingdale House of Music, Tax Information, 1970-1973 (Box 154, Folder 1028)
    - (Republic of) Botswana, 1974-April 1975 (Box 154, Folder 1029)
    - (Republic of) Botswana, 1975 May-1976 December (Box 154, Folder 1030)
    - (Republic of) Botswana, 1977-June 1978 (Box 155, Folder 1031)
    - (Republic of) Botswana, 1978 July-1979 (Box 155, Folder 1032)
    - (Republic of) Botswana, Supplementary Materials, 1970-1975 (Box 155, Folder 1033)
    - (The) Botswana Society, 1972-1976 (Box 155, Folder 1034)
    - (The) Botswana Society, Tax Information, 1972-1974 (Box 155, Folder 1035)
    - (The) Botswana Society, Supplementary Materials, Notes and Records (Box 155, Folder 1036)
    - Boy Scouts of America, Greater New York Councils, 1941-1954 (Box 155, Folder 1037)
    - Boy Scouts of America, Greater New York Councils, 1955-1961 (Box 155, Folder 1038)
    - Boy Scouts of America, Greater New York Councils, 1962-1967 (Box 156, Folder 1039)
    - Boy Scouts of America, Greater New York Councils, 1967-1968 (Box 156, Folder 1040)
    - Boy Scouts of America, Greater New York Councils, 1968-1969 (Box 156, Folder 1041)
    - Boy Scouts of America, Greater New York Councils, 1970-1976 (Box 156, Folder 1042)
    - Boy Scouts of America, Greater New York Councils, Tax Information, 1970-1974 (Box 156, Folder 1043)
    - Boy Scouts of America, Katahdin Area Council, 1972-1974 (Box 156, Folder 1044)
    - Boy Scouts of America, Katahdin Area Council, Tax Information, 1972-1973 (Box 156, Folder 1045)
    - Boy Scouts of America, Washington Irving Council, Inc., 1966-1969 (Box 156, Folder 1046)
    - Boy Scouts of America, National Council, 1958-1969 (Box 157, Folder 1047)
    - Boy Scouts of America, National Council, 1970-1971 (Box 157, Folder 1048)
    - Boy Scouts of America, National Council, Tax Information, 1970-1971 (Box 157, Folder 1049)
    - Boy Scouts of America, National Council, 1972-1977 (Box 157, Folder 1050)
    - Boys Club of New York, Inc., East Village Girls Club, 1969 (Box 158, Folder 1051)
    - Boys Harbor, Inc., 1978-1980 (Box 158, Folder 1052)
    - The Bridge, Inc., 1960-1969 (Box 158, Folder 1053)
    - The Bridge, Inc., 1970-1975 (Box 158, Folder 1054)
    - The Bridge, Inc., 1976 (Box 158, Folder 1055)
    - The Bridge, Inc., Tax Information, 1971 (Box 158, Folder 1056)
    - British War Relief Society, Inc., 1941-1942 (Box 158, Folder 1057)
    - British-American Associates, 1975-1976 (Box 158, Folder 1058)
    - British-American Associates, 1977 (Box 158, Folder 1059)
    - British-American Associates, Tax Information, 1976 (Box 158, Folder 1060)
    - British-American Associates, Supplementary Materials, 1976-1977 (Box 158, Folder 1061)
    - Broad Jump, Inc., 1970-1976 (Box 158, Folder 1062)
    - Broad Jump, Inc., 1977 (Box 159, Folder 1063)
    - Broad Jump, Inc., Tax Information, 1971 (Box 159, Folder 1064)
    - Broadcast Institute of North America, 1966-1967 (Box 159, Folder 1065)
    - Broadcast Institute of North America, 1968-1969 (Box 159, Folder 1066)
    - Broadcast Institute of North America, 1970 (Box 159, Folder 1067)
    - Broadcast Institute of North America, 1971 (Box 159, Folder 1068)
    - Broadcast Institute of North America, 1972-May 1973 (Box 160, Folder 1069)
    - Broadcast Institute of North America, 1973-1974 (Box 160, Folder 1070)
    - Broadcast Institute of North America, Tax Information, 1971-1975 (Box 160, Folder 1071)
    - Broadcast Institute of North America, Supplementary Information, 1972 (Box 160, Folder 1072)
    - Bronx Frontier Development Corporation, 1977 January-April (Box 160, Folder 1073)
    - Bronx Frontier Development Corporation, 1977 May-1978 April (Box 160, Folder 1074)
    - Bronx Frontier Development Corporation, 1978 May-1979 (Box 161, Folder 1075)
    - Bronx Frontier Development Corporation, 1980-1982 (Box 161, Folder 1076)
    - Bronx River Neighborhood Center, 1967-1969 (Box 161, Folder 1077)
    - Bronx River Neighborhood Center, 1970-1974 (Box 161, Folder 1078)
    - Bronx River Neighborhood Center, 1977-1979 (Box 161, Folder 1079)
    - Bronx River Neighborhood Center, Tax Information, 1970-1972 (Box 161, Folder 1080)
    - Bronx River Neighborhood Center, Resource Recovery Compost Operation, 1977 (Box 162, Folder 1081)
    - Brookings Institution, 1953-1961 (Box 162, Folder 1082)
    - Brookings Institution, 1962-1963 (Box 162, Folder 1083)
    - Brookings Institution, 1964 (Box 162, Folder 1084)
    - Brookings Institution, 1965-1969 (Box 162, Folder 1085)
    - Brookings Institution, 1970-1974 (Box 163, Folder 1086)
    - Brookings Institution, 1975-1976 (Box 163, Folder 1087)
    - Brookings Institution, 1977 January-May (Box 163, Folder 1088)
    - Brookings Institution, A Study of the Labor Certification Program, 1977 (Box 163, Folder 1089)
    - Brookings Institution, 1977 April (Box 164, Folder 1090)
    - Brookings Institution, 1977 June (Box 164, Folder 1091)
    - Brookings Institution, 1977 December-1978 (Box 164, Folder 1092)
    - Brookings Institution, 1979 (Box 164, Folder 1093)
    - Brookings Institution, 1980 (Box 165, Folder 1094)
    - Brookings Institution, 1981-1982 (Box 165, Folder 1095)
    - Brookings Institution, The Social and Economic Responsibility of Business, 1970-1976 (Box 165, Folder 1096)
    - Brookings Institution, The Social and Economic Responsibility of Business, Tax Information, 1971-1973 (Box 165, Folder 1097)
    - Brookings Institution, Materials on the Conference held at Williamsburg on East Asia, 1981 (Box 165, Folder 1098)
    - Brookings Institution, Materials on the Conference held at Williamsburg on East Asia, 1981 (Box 165, Folder 1099)
    - Brookings Institution, Materials on the Conference held at Williamsburg on East Asia, Supplementary Materials, 1970-1982 (Box 165, Folder 1100)
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music, 1970-1976 (Box 166, Folder 1101)
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music, 1977-1979 (Box 166, Folder 1102)
    - Brooklyn Arts and Culture Association, Inc., 1973-1976 (Box 166, Folder 1103)
    - Brooklyn Arts and Culture Association, Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 166, Folder 1104)
    - Brooklyn Arts and Culture Association, Inc., Tax Information, 1976-1977 (Box 166, Folder 1105)
    - Brooklyn Bureau of Community Service (formerly: Brooklyn Bureau of Social Service and Children's Aid Society), 1941-1958 (Box 167, Folder 1106)
    - Brooklyn Bureau of Community Service, 1959-1963 (Box 167, Folder 1107)
    - Brooklyn Bureau of Community Service, 1964-1966 (Box 167, Folder 1108)
    - Brooklyn Bureau of Community Service, 1966-1969 (Box 167, Folder 1109)
    - Brooklyn Bureau of Community Service, 1970-1973 (Box 168, Folder 1110)
    - Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences, 1952-1959 (Box 168, Folder 1111)
    - Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences, 1960-1965 (Box 168, Folder 1112)
    - Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences, 1966-1969 (Box 169, Folder 1113)
    - Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences, 1970-1972 (Box 169, Folder 1114)
    - Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences, 1972-1975 (Box 169, Folder 1115)
    - Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences, 1973-1975 (Box 169, Folder 1116)
    - Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences, Tax Information, 1970-1973 (Box 169, Folder 1117)
    - Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences, Children's Museum, Supplementary Materials, 1950-1952, 1967 (Box 169, Folder 1118)
    - Brooklyn Institutional Council, 1970-1973 (Box 170, Folder 1118A)
    - Brooklyn Institutional Council, Tax Information, 1970-1973 (Box 170, Folder 1119)
    - (Frederic Burk Foundation for Education, removed to Box 245) (Box 170, Folder 1120-1122)
    - Business Committee for the Arts, 1967-1969 (Box 170, Folder 1123)
    - Business Committee for the Arts, 1970-1971 (Box 170, Folder 1124)
    - Business Committee for the Arts, 1972-1974 (Box 171, Folder 1125)
    - Business Committee for the Arts, Tax Information, 1970-1972 (Box 171, Folder 1126)
    - Business Committee for the Arts, Supplementary Materials, 1969-1970 (Box 171, Folder 1127)
    - Christian Action for Development in the Caribbean (CADEC, Inc., Ltd.), 1976-1977 (Box 171, Folder 1128A)
    - Christian Action for Development in the Caribbean (CADEC, Inc., Ltd.), 1977 (Box 171, Folder 1128B)
    - Christian Action for Development in the Caribbean (CADEC, Inc., Ltd.), 1978 (Box 171, Folder 1129)
    - Christian Action for Development in the Caribbean (CADEC, Inc., Ltd.), 1979 (Box 172, Folder 1130)
    - Christian Action for Development in the Caribbean (CADEC, Inc., Ltd.), 1980 January-May (Box 172, Folder 1131)
    - Christian Action for Development in the Caribbean (CADEC, Inc., Ltd.), 1980 June (Box 172, Folder 1132)
    - Christian Action for Development in the Caribbean (CADEC, Inc., Ltd.), 1980 July-1981 June (Box 173, Folder 1133)
    - Christian Action for Development in the Caribbean (CADEC, Inc., Ltd.), 1981 July-August (Box 173, Folder 1134)
    - Christian Action for Development in the Caribbean (CADEC, Inc., Ltd.), 1981 December (Box 173, Folder 1135)
    - Christian Action for Development in the Caribbean (CADEC, Inc., Ltd.), 1982 (Box 173, Folder 1136)
    - (Regents of the University of) California, Berkeley, 1974-June 1975 (Box 174, Folder 1137)
    - (Regents of the University of) California, Berkeley, 1975 August-December (Box 174, Folder 1138)
    - (Regents of the University of) California, Berkeley, 1976 (Box 174, Folder 1139)
    - (Regents of the University of) California, Los Angeles, 1950-1969 (Box 174, Folder 1140)
    - (Regents of the University of) California, Los Angeles, Upper Volta Sound Archives Project, 1969 (Box 174, Folder 1141)
    - (Regents of the University of) California, Los Angeles, Upper Volta Sound Archives Project, 1970-1975 (Box 174, Folder 1142)
    - (Regents of the University of) California, Los Angeles, Upper Volta Sound Archives Project, 1977-197? #2-4/14/1908 (Box 175, Folder 1143)
    - (Regents of the University of) California, Los Angeles, Upper Volta Sound Archives Project, 1980 (Box 175, Folder 1144)
    - (Regents of the University of) California, Los Angeles, Upper Volta Sound Archives Project, Tax Information, 1973-1974 (Box 175, Folder 1145)
    - Cambridge College, 1977-1980 (Box 175, Folder 1146)
    - Cambridge College, 1981 (Box 175, Folder 1147)
    - Cambridge School, 1976 (Box 175, Folder 1148)
    - Cambridge School, 1977-1978 (Box 175, Folder 1149)
    - Cambridge School, Tax Information, 1976-1979 (Box 175, Folder 1150)
    - Canadian Arctic Resources Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 175, Folder 1151)
    - Canadian Arctic Resources Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 175, Folder 1152)
    - Canadian Arctic Resources Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 175, Folder 1153)
    - Canadian Arctic Resources Committee, Tax Information, 1975-1977 (Box 175, Folder 1154)
    - Canadian Institute of International Affairs, 1968-1969 (Box 176, Folder 1155)
    - Canadian Institute of International Affairs, 1970-1976 (Box 176, Folder 1156)
    - Canadian Institute of International Affairs, 1977-1981 (Box 176, Folder 1157)
    - Canadian Institute of International Affairs, Tax Information, 1969-1975 (Box 176, Folder 1158)
    - Capital Formation Inc., 1971-1972 (Box 176, Folder 1159)
    - Capital Formation Inc., 1973-1974 (Box 176, Folder 1160)
    - Capital Formation Inc., Tax Information, 1972-1973 (Box 176, Folder 1161)
    - Career Center for Social Services of Greater New York, Inc. (formerly: Social Work Recruiting Center of Greater New York Inc.; formerly: Social Work Recruiting Committee of Greater New York, Inc.), 1957-1965 (Box 176, Folder 1162)
    - Career Center for Social Services of Greater New York, Inc., 1965 (Box 177, Folder 1163)
    - Career Center for Social Services of Greater New York, Inc., 1966-1967 (Box 177, Folder 1164)
    - Career Center for Social Services of Greater New York, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 177, Folder 1165)
    - Career Center for Social Services of Greater New York, Inc., 1970-1972 (Box 177, Folder 1166)
    - Caribbean Agro-Economic Society, 1976-1981 (Box 177, Folder 1167)
    - Caribbean Agro-Economic Society, Tax Information, 1977-1978 (Box 177, Folder 1168)
    - Caribbean Conservation Association, 1975-1977 (Box 177, Folder 1169)
    - Caribbean Conservation Association, 1977 (Box 177, Folder 1170)
      8 photographs relocated to Rockefeller Brothers Fund photographs box 1494
    - Caribbean Conservation Association, 1978 (Box 178, Folder 1171)
    - Caribbean Conservation Association, 1978 (Box 178, Folder 1172)
    - Caribbean Conservation Association, 1978 (Box 178, Folder 1173)
    - Caribbean Conservation Association, 1979 (Box 178, Folder 1174)
    - Caribbean Conservation Association, 1979 (Box 178, Folder 1175)
    - Caribbean Conservation Association, 1979 (Box 178, Folder 1176)
    - Caribbean Conservation Association, 1979 (Box 179, Folder 1177)
    - Caribbean Conservation Association, 1979 (Box 179, Folder 1178)
    - Carnegie Corporation of New York, General, 1953-1976 (Box 179, Folder 1179)
    - Carnegie Corporation of New York, The Greenbrier Group, 1958-1959 (Box 179, Folder 1180)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1953-1969 (Box 179, Folder 1181)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1970-1976 (Box 180, Folder 1182)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, Committee on Foreign Affairs Personnel, 1961-1966 (Box 180, Folder 1183)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, Cook Survey, 1963-1964 (Box 180, Folder 1184)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, Cook Survey - Survey and Addendum, 1963-1964 (Box 180, Folder 1185)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, International Fact-Finding Center, 1973-1976 (Box 181, Folder 1186)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, International Fact-Finding Center, 1977-1979 (Box 181, Folder 1187)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, International Visitor's Bureau (formerly: United Nations Hospitality Information Service, 1960-1961 (Box 181, Folder 1188)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, International Visitor's Bureau, 1962-1965 (Box 181, Folder 1189)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, United Nations Area Study - Tax Information, 1965-1966 (Box 182, Folder 1190)
    - Carnegie-Mellon University, 1958-1969 (Box 182, Folder 1191)
    - Carnegie-Mellon University, 1958-1969 (Box 182, Folder 1192)
    - Carnegie-Mellon University, Reprint Series by Margaret Morrison Carnegie College, 1966-1968 (Box 182, Folder 1193)
    - Carnegie-Mellon University, Reprint Series by Margaret Morrison Carnegie College, 1966-1968 (Box 182, Folder 1194)
    - (Rachel) Carson Trust for the Living Environment, Inc., 1977-1979 (Box 183, Folder 1195)
    - (Rachel) Carson Trust for the Living Environment, Inc., Tax Information, 1977 (Box 183, Folder 1196)
    - Catalyst, 1963-1969 (Box 183, Folder 1197)
    - Catalyst, 1970-1976 (Box 183, Folder 1198)
    - Cathedral Church of St. John the Divine, 1974-1976 (Box 183, Folder 1199)
    - Cathedral Church of St. John the Divine, 1977-1979 (Box 184, Folder 1200)
    - Catholic Charities of the Archdiocese of New York, 1946-1965 (Box 184, Folder 1201)
    - Catholic Charities of the Archdiocese of New York, 1966-1969 (Box 184, Folder 1202)
    - Catholic Charities of the Archdiocese of New York, 1970-1976 (Box 184, Folder 1203)
    - Catholic Charities of the Archdiocese of New York, Tax Information, 1970-1974 (Box 184, Folder 1204)
    - Catholic Foreign Mission Society of America, Inc., 1965-1969 (Box 184, Folder 1205)
    - Catholic Foreign Mission Society of America, Inc., 1970-1972 (Box 184, Folder 1206)
    - Catholic University of America, 1956-1969 (Box 185, Folder 1207)
    - Catholic University of America, 1970-1972 (Box 185, Folder 1208)
    - Catholic University of America, 1973-1974 (Box 185, Folder 1209)
    - Catholic University of America, 1974 (Box 185, Folder 1210)
    - Catholic University of America, 1975 January-September (Box 186, Folder 1211)
    - Catholic University of America, 1975 October-December (Box 186, Folder 1212)
    - Catholic University of America, 1976 (Box 186, Folder 1213)
    - Catholic University of America, 1977 (Box 186, Folder 1214)
    - Catholic University of America, 1978-1979 (Box 187, Folder 1215)
    - Center for the Arts at Ithaca, Inc. (formerly: Ithaca Festival of the Classics, Inc.), 1965-1975 (Box 187, Folder 1216)
    - Center for Community Change, 1969 (Box 187, Folder 1217)
    - Center for Community Change, 1970-1972 (Box 187, Folder 1218)
    - Center for Community Change, 1973 (Box 187, Folder 1219)
    - Center for Community Change, 1974-1975 (Box 188, Folder 1220)
    - Center for Community Change, 1976 (Box 188, Folder 1221)
    - Center for Community Change, 1977 (Box 188, Folder 1222)
    - Center for Community Change, 1978 January-September (Box 189, Folder 1223)
    - Center for Community Change, 1978 September-1979 September (Box 189, Folder 1224)
    - Center for Community Change, 1978 October-December (Box 189, Folder 1225)
    - Center for Community Change, 1980 (Box 189, Folder 1226)
    - Center for Community Change, 1981 January-April (Box 190, Folder 1227)
    - Center for Community Change, 1981 May-December (Box 190, Folder 1228)
    - Center for Community Change, 1982 (Box 190, Folder 1229)
    - Center for Community Change, National Committee for Responsive Philanthropy, 1976 (Box 190, Folder 1230)
    - Center for Community Change, National Committee for Responsive Philanthropy, 1977-1978 (Box 190, Folder 1231)
    - Center for Community Change, National Committee for Responsive Philanthropy, Tax Information, 1976-1978 (Box 190, Folder 1232)
    - Center of Concern, 1973-1974 (Box 191, Folder 1233)
    - Center of Concern, 1975 January-May (Box 191, Folder 1234)
    - Center of Concern, 1975 June-December (Box 191, Folder 1235)
    - Center of Concern, 1976 (Box 191, Folder 1236)
    - Center of Concern, Tax Information, 1973-1976 (Box 191, Folder 1237)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc., 1966-1967 (Box 191, Folder 1238)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc., 1968 (Box 192, Folder 1239)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc., 1969 (Box 192, Folder 1240)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 192, Folder 1241)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 192, Folder 1242)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc., 1974 (Box 192, Folder 1243)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc., 1975 (Box 193, Folder 1244)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc., 1976 (Box 193, Folder 1245)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc., 1977 (Box 193, Folder 1246)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc., 1978 (Box 193, Folder 1247)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc., 1979 (Box 193, Folder 1248)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations, Arts International, 1978 (Box 193, Folder 1249)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations, Arts International, 1979 (Box 194, Folder 1250)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations, Arts International, 1980 (Box 194, Folder 1251)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations, Arts International, 1981 (Box 194, Folder 1252)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations, Arts International, 1982 (Box 194, Folder 1253)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1968 (Box 194, Folder 1254)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1969 January-June (Box 194, Folder 1255)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1969 July-December (Box 194, Folder 1256)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1970 (Box 195, Folder 1257)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1971 (Box 195, Folder 1258)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1972 (Box 195, Folder 1259)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1973 (Box 195, Folder 1260)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1974 (Box 195, Folder 1261)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1975 January-June (Box 196, Folder 1262)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1975 July-December (Box 196, Folder 1263)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1976 January-June (Box 196, Folder 1264)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1976 July-December (Box 196, Folder 1265)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1977 (Box 197, Folder 1266)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1978 (Box 197, Folder 1267)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1979 January-June (Box 197, Folder 1268)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1979 July-December (Box 197, Folder 1269)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1980-1981 (Box 198, Folder 1270)
    - Center for Law and Social Policy, 1982 (Box 198, Folder 1271)
    - Center for Neighborhood Technology, 1982 (Box 198, Folder 1272)
      94 photographs with negatives relocated to Rockefeller Brothers Fund photographs box 1494
    - Center for Neighborhood Technology, 1983 January-June (Box 198, Folder 1273)
    - Center for Neighborhood Technology, 1983 July-December (Box 198, Folder 1274)
    - Center for Neighborhood Technology, 1984 (Box 198, Folder 1275)
    - Center for Policy Research, Inc., 1971-1976 (Box 199, Folder 1276)
    - Center for Policy Research, Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 199, Folder 1277)
    - Center for Policy Research, Inc., Report: "Enterprise in the Non-Profit Sector", 1982 (Box 199, Folder 1278)
    - Center for Public Resources, Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 199, Folder 1279)
    - Center for Public Resources, Inc., 1978 (Box 200, Folder 1280)
    - Center for Public Resources, Inc., 1979 (Box 200, Folder 1281)
    - Center for Public Resources, Inc., 1980 January-June (Box 200, Folder 1282)
    - Center for Public Resources, Inc., 1980 July-December (Box 200, Folder 1283)
    - Center for Public Resources, Inc., 1981 (Box 200, Folder 1284)
    - Center for the Study of Public Policy, 1970-1976 (Box 201, Folder 1285)
    - Center for the Study of Public Policy, 1977-1978 (Box 201, Folder 1286)
    - Center for the Study of Public Policy, 1980-1982 (Box 201, Folder 1287)
    - Centre College of Kentucky, 1980-1981 (Box 201, Folder 1288)
    - Centre for Educational Television Overseas, 1965 (Box 201, Folder 1289)
    - Centre for Educational Television Overseas, 1966 (Box 201, Folder 1290)
    - Centre for Educational Television Overseas, 1967 (Box 201, Folder 1291)
    - Centre for Educational Television Overseas, 1968 (Box 202, Folder 1292)
    - Centre for Educational Television Overseas, 1969 (Box 202, Folder 1293)
    - Centre for Educational Television Overseas, Background Material, 1966-1969 (Box 202, Folder 1294)
    - Centre for Educational Television Overseas, Background Material for Pledge and Payment / Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 202, Folder 1295)
    - Chamber Music Society of Lincoln Center, Inc., 1969 (Box 202, Folder 1296)
    - Chamber Music Society of Lincoln Center, Inc., 1970-1979 (Box 202, Folder 1297)
    - Chamber Music Society of Lincoln Center, Inc., 1970-1972 (Box 202, Folder 1298)
    - Chelsea Theater Center, 1967-1969 (Box 202, Folder 1299)
    - Chelsea Theater Center, 1970-1976 (Box 202, Folder 1300)